supercuts.com 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy | Supercuts

Last Updated: January 1, 2019

This Online Privacy Policy applies to information about you, including personal information, that Regis Corporation and its subsidiaries or affiliates (collectively, “Regis”) may obtain when you visit a website, mobile application, or other online property that links to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Sites”).  In this Privacy Policy, we describe how Regis may collect information about you through the Sites; how we may use and share such information; how we safeguard the information we collect; and how you may contact us regarding our privacy practices.

Please read this Privacy Policy before using the Sites or submitting any personal information. By continuing to use the Sites, you acknowledge that information we obtain through the Sites will be governed by the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may update or change this Privacy Policy from time to time.  If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of this page. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit the Sites to stay informed about our information practices.

For information regarding how Regis handles personal information of Canadian residents, please view the  **Canadian Privacy Policy**.

**Information Collection**

**_Information You Provide_**

Regis may collect information voluntarily submitted by visitors to the Sites, including personal information. For example, the Sites may include web pages or registration forms through which you may provide personal information to contact us or to sign up for an account. “Personal information” means information that may be used to identify you as an individual, such as your name, telephone number, email address, postal address, or any other personal information you choose to include in messages, comments, or other open-field text boxes.

  * If you purchase our gift cards online, you may also provide us your personal information or the personal information of an individual other than yourself if you wish to send that individual a gift card.
    * If you provide someone else’s personal information, such as their name and email address, you represent to us that you have that individual’s permission to share such personal information.
    * Gift card purchases are managed and facilitated by a third-party vendor and may require you provide the vendor your payment information. We do not receive from the vendor or otherwise process your payment information.
  * Certain features on the Sites allow you to record audio messages or to upload images or photos from your device or through a connection to a third-party website (e.g., Facebook, Instagram).
  * You may provide us employment history, professional license information, and other relevant information when you apply for a job via the Sites.
    * You may provide us this personal information directly or via a third party service provider we engage for this purpose.
    * When applying for a job, you may provide additional personal information using a chatbot feature that is operated by a third party.

You are not required to submit your personal information; however, not doing so may limit your ability to use certain functions or to request certain services or information on the Sites.

**_Information Collected Automatically_**

In addition to information that you submit to us, we may collect certain information using automated means such as cookies, web beacons, and web server logs. The types of information we collect automatically include IP addresses, device identifiers, browser characteristics, operating system details, language preferences, referring URLs, length of visits, and pages viewed. We may obtain geolocation information about you to allow map or salon-finding features to function properly. We may combine this automatically-collected information with other information we obtain about you.

Information about your use of the Sites and other online locations may be collected across time, devices, and websites, and used for numerous purposes including to associate different devices you use and to deliver relevant and/or retargeted content, including interest-based ads.

**_Data Analytics_**

The Sites may use third-party web analytics services, such as Adobe Analytics and Google Analytics, to help us analyze how visitors use the Sites. These services track information about visitors including IP addresses, browser types, referring pages, pages visited, and time spent on particular pages, which we use to improve and tailor the user experience on our Sites.  For further information about Adobe Analytics and how they use analytics data, [ **click here**](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/analytics.html). To go directly to an opt-out tool for Adobe Analytics, [ **click here**](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html#4). To learn more about opting out of data collection through Google Analytics, [ **click here**](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

We may also collect certain aggregate, non-identifying information (such as what web browsers are used by visitors to the Sites and what websites are referring traffic or linking to the Sites). We do not limit the ways we may use or share these types of statistical and/or aggregate information.

Your web browser may have settings that allow you to transmit a “Do Not Track” signal when you visit various websites or use online services.  Like many websites, the Sites are not designed to respond to “Do Not Track” signals received from browsers.  To learn more about “Do Not Track” signals, [ **click here**](https://allaboutdnt.com/).

Third parties may collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use the Sites.

**Information Use**

We may use personal information we obtain through the Sites for a number of purposes, including:

  * To respond to emails or other requests, comments, or questions;
  * To improve the Sites and to personalize our visitors’ experiences on the Sites;
  * To provide customer support;
  * To provide you with information that we believe may be useful to you, such as the location of nearby stores and information about products or services offered by us or others;
  * To process job applications or related inquiries for current or future employment opportunities;
  * To comply with applicable laws, regulations, or legal process as well as industry standards and our company policies;
  * To prevent fraud or other misuse, including by protecting our rights and the rights of affiliates or related third parties;
  * To allow you to set appointments, check in for appointments, or for other appointment-related purposes, such as to send you reminders about upcoming appointments;
  * To maintain records of our transactions and communications;
  * To monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities of visitors to the Sites;
  * As otherwise necessary or useful to conduct our business, so long as such use is permitted by law; or
  * For any other purpose, with your consent.

In addition, we use certain information collected online through cookies, web beacons, and other automated means for purposes such as recognizing your computer when you visit the Sites, tracking your activity as you navigate the Sites, or analyzing your use of the Sites. This information may be used to track your activity over time on various websites and services, as well as across different devices you may use to access the Internet.

We also may use the information we obtain about you in other ways for which we provide notice at the time of collection.

**Information Sharing**

Our employees and agents may have access to personal information collected through the Sites in the course of operating our businesses. For example, if you were to send us an email asking a question, we would provide your query and email address to one of our employees so that the employee could send you a reply. We also may share personal information with our affiliates, franchisees, or related business units.

We may permit vendors, consultants, and other service providers to access information collected through the Sites to carry out work on our behalf. For example, we may hire outside companies to help us send emails and manage email campaigns, run survey programs, or host or operate our Sites or mobile applications. These third party service providers use the personal information to which they have access to carry out the limited purposes for which we shared the information.

We also may share your information (1) if we are required to do so by law, regulation, or legal process (such as in response to a court order, search warrant, or subpoena); (2) to fulfill requests by government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities; (3) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity; or (4) to enforce our policies, or protect rights, property, or safety. We may cooperate with law enforcement authorities in the investigation and prosecution of violations of our rules, behavior that is harmful to other visitors, or is illegal.

We reserve the right to transfer any information we obtain through the Sites in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (e.g., further to a merger, reorganization, liquidation, or any other business transaction). Such transfers also may include providing information we obtain through the Sites to our franchisees.

**Social Features**

The Sites may include features that are designed to permit interactions that you initiate between the Sites and third party websites or services, including third party social networks (“Social Features”). Examples of Social Features include enabling you to log in to the Sites with the username and password you use with a third party site or service; to “like” or “share” our content on other websites or services; or to transmit content to our Sites from your account on a third party website or service.

If you choose to use Social Features on the Sites, information you post or provide access to may be publicly displayed on the Sites or by the provider of the Social Feature that you use. Similarly, if you post information on a third party platform that references one of our Sites (e.g., by using a hashtag associated with Regis in a tweet or status update), your post may be published on our Sites in accordance with the terms of the third party website or service. Also, both Regis and the third party may have access to certain information about you and your use of both the Sites and the third party site or service. In addition, we may receive information about you if other users of a third party website allow us to access their profiles and you are one of their “connections,” or if information about you is otherwise accessible through those individuals’ profiles or pages on a social networking or other third party website or interactive service.

The information we collect in connection with Social Features is subject to this Privacy Policy. The information collected and stored by the third parties remains subject to those third parties’ privacy practices, including whether the third parties continue to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices with regard to what is visible to others on those third party websites or services.

**Your Choices**

Many web browsers include options that allow users to disable existing cookies or stop accepting new cookies. Please note that if you disable cookies certain features on the Sites may not work properly, and disabling cookies may invalidate opt outs that rely on cookies to function.

You may request that we update, correct, or delete personal information that you have submitted to us or that we have collected through the Sites by emailing [ **departmentcs@regiscorp.com**](mailto:departmentcs@regiscorp.com) (include “Privacy Inquiry” in the subject line of your email. To help protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to verify your identity prior to honoring any such requests.

If you create a personal profile or account on the Sites, you have the option to review, edit, or delete information you submit by logging in and following links to the pages that list options for managing user accounts.

You can opt out of receiving promotional email communications from us by following the instructions provided in those communications, or by logging into your account and altering your preferences. Please note that even if you opt out of receiving promotional communications, we may continue to send you non-promotional emails, such as emails regarding our ongoing business relations.

With respect to geolocation data, you may restrict the collection of geolocation information about your device by altering the settings on your mobile device (for our mobile applications) or the settings on your browser (for our websites). For example, for mobile applications, you may choose to allow geolocation data to be collected only while you are using the mobile app, or you may disable geolocation services altogether. Disabling geolocation services will limit the functionality of our app.

You may choose whether to receive some interest-based advertising by submitting opt-outs.  Some of the advertisers and service providers that perform advertising-related services for us and for third parties may participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising.  To learn more about how you can exercise certain choices regarding interest-based advertising, visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, and <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices>_._ Some of these companies may also be members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). To learn more about the NAI and your opt-out options for their members, see _<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>_.  Please be aware that, even if you are able to opt out of certain kinds of interest-based advertising through these organizations, you may continue to receive other types of ads.

Please note: If your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit these opt-out webpages, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different device or web browser, or use a non-browser-based method of access (e.g., mobile app), your NAI / DAA browser-based opt-out may not, or may no longer, be effective. We are not responsible for the effectiveness of, or compliance with, any third-parties’ opt-out options or programs or the accuracy of their statements regarding their programs.

In addition, we may serve ads on third-party services (such as Facebook) that are targeted to reach users on those services who are also listed in one or more of our databases (“Matched List Ads”). This is done by matching common factors between our databases and the databases of the third-party services. If we use Facebook to serve Matched List Ads on Facebook, you should be able to hover over the box in the right corner of such a Facebook ad to find out how to opt out of our list. If you opt out from our Facebook Matched List Ads, we will remove the matching personal information from that list, however, this will not take effect immediately and if you have multiple accounts with us you may have to opt out separately for each one. We are not responsible for third parties’ data security practices, failure to comply with opt-out instructions, or any inaccurate information they may provide about our Matched List Ads practices.

**Security**

We maintain appropriate physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards designed to protect personal information collected and received through the Sites. Although we use reasonable efforts to secure such information, transmission via the Internet is not completely secure, and we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to us through the Sites.

**Links to Other Websites**

The Sites may include links to other websites for your convenience and information. Those linked websites may be operated by unaffiliated entities, and may have their own privacy policies or notices. If you link to other websites, please review the privacy policies posted on those sites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of websites that we do not control.  Please be aware that websites operated by our franchisees are not governed by this Privacy Policy. 

**Children’s Online Privacy**

The Sites are not intended for children, nor are they targeted to children under the age of thirteen (13). We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 through the Sites, and if we learn that we have received information from a visitor under the age of 13, we will delete such information in accordance with applicable law.

**Sweepstakes and Contests**

If you participate in certain activities through the Sites, such as sweepstakes, contests, or surveys (“Contests”), the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by any specific terms posted in conjunction with the relevant Contest. Contests that are managed by third-party vendors on our behalf will be governed by the relevant vendor’s terms and privacy policy.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

We may from time to time elect to share certain personal information (as defined by California’s “Shine the Light” law) about you with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. California law permits customers in California to request certain details about how their personal information (as that term is defined by the relevant statute) is shared with third parties and, in some cases, affiliates for direct marketing purposes. If this applies, you may obtain the categories of personal information shared and the names and addresses of third parties that received personal information for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately prior calendar year (e.g. requests made in 2018 will receive information about 2017 sharing activities). To make such a request, please provide sufficient information for us to determine if this applies to you, attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response.  You may make this request by writing to: Regis Corporation, 7201 Metro Blvd, Minneapolis, MN 55439 (Attention: Department CS – Privacy Inquiry), or by emailing departmentcs@regiscorp.com.  Any such request must include “California Privacy Rights Request” in the first line of the description and include your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code.  Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year. 

**Information for Users Outside the United States**

If you are visiting any of the Sites from outside the United States, please be aware that information we collect through the Sites may be transferred to and stored on our servers in the United States. By using the Sites, you acknowledge and consent to the transfer and processing of your personal data in the United States as described in this Privacy Policy. The data protection laws and regulations applicable to your personal data transferred to the United States may be different from the laws in your country of residence.

Visitors from Canada, please refer to our  **Canadian Privacy Policy**.

**Contact Us**

To contact us regarding this Privacy Policy or with questions about our privacy practices, you may email us at [ **departmentcs@regiscorp.com**](mailto:departmentcs@regiscorp.com) (please include “Privacy Inquiry” in the subject line of your email), call us at 1-800-737-3535, or send postal mail to:

Regis Corporation  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
7201 Metro Blvd  
Minneapolis, MN 55439
